{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043880497","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043880497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" d0e23d59-e617-4ad9-a395-31e5327269ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043885790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043885790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 2f79862f-c073-423b-8799-5f654a426d8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043899837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043899837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 2f79862f-c073-423b-8799-5f654a426d8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043902431","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043902430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 2f79862f-c073-423b-8799-5f654a426d8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043902569","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043902568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 2f79862f-c073-423b-8799-5f654a426d8a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043924530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043924530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_g_l"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043931168","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043931168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_l_b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043938765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043938765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_l_b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043945430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043945430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_n_b"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043952077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043952076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_ch_a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043958725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043958725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_ch_y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043965366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043965366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043972833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043972833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043983320","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043983320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043989963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043989963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_y_d"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549043996604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549043996604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_h_ch"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044004076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044004076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_h_ch"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044010708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044010708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_h_ch"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044017388","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044017388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_h_v"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044024856","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044024856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_h_v"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044035067","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044035066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_h_v"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044041270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044041270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044048756","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044048755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044054936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044054935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_205719"," gameId":" 02fdce1c-d6dc-4a1f-9609-a4e896070515"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_l_w_i"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}